<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<root version="3.3" release="8|CoreRPG:3" integrity="4d2824c190e3306e9b9df42cdb403089596a54ca">
	<encounter>
		<category name="00. Curse of Strahd" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="01. Chapter 1: Into the Mists" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="02. Chapter 2: The Lands of Barovia" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="03. Chapter 3: The Village of Barovia" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="04. Chapter 4: Castle Ravenloft" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="05. Chapter 5: The Town of Vallaki" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="06. Chapter 6: Old Bonegrinder" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="07. Chapter 7: Argynvostholt" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="08. Chapter 8: The Village of Krezk" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="09. Chapter 9: Tsolenka Pass" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="10. Chapter 10: The Ruins of Berez" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="11. Chapter 11: Van Richten's Tower" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="12. Chapter 12: The Wizard of Wines" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="13. Chapter 13: The Amber Temple" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="14. Chapter 14: Yester Hill" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="15. Chapter 15: Werewolf Den" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="16. Epilogue" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="17. Appendix A: Character Options" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="18. Appendix B: Death House" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<enc_18_03_09_secretroom>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>9. Secret Room</h>
					<p>This secret room contains bookshelves packed with tomes describing fiend-summoning rituals and the necromantic rituals of a cult called the Priests of Osybus. The rituals are bogus, which any character can ascertain after studying the books for 1 hour and succeeding on a DC 12 Intelligence (Arcana) check.</p>
					<p>A heavy wooden chest with clawed iron feet stands against the south wall, its lid half-closed. Sticking out of the chest is a skeleton in leather armor. Close inspection reveals that the skeleton belongs to a human who triggered a poisoned dart trap. Three darts are stuck in the dead adventurer's armor and ribcage. The dart-firing mechanism inside the chest no longer functions.</p>
					<p>Clutched in the skeleton's left hand is a letter bearing the seal of Strahd von Zarovich, which athe adventurer tried to remove from the chest. Written in flowing script, the letter reads as follows:</p>
					<frame>My most pathetic servant,&#13;I am not a messiah sent to you by the Dark Powers of this land. I have not come to lead you on a path to immortality. However many souls you have bled on your hidden altar, however many visitors you have tortured in your dungeon, know that you are not the ones who brought me to this beautiful land. You are but worms writhing in my earth.&#13;You say that you are cursed, your fortunes spent. You abandoned love for madness, took solace in the bosom of another woman, and sired a stillborn son. Cursed by darkness? Of that I have no doubt. Save you from your wretchedness? I think not. I much prefer you as you are.&#13;&#13;Your dread lord and master,&#13;Strahd von Zarovich</frame>
					<h>Treasure</h>
					<p>The chest contains three blank books with black leather covers (worth 25 gp each), three <i>spell scrolls </i>( <i>bless, protection from poison, </i>and <i>spiritual weapon </i>), the deed to the house, the deed to a windmill, and a signed will. The windmill referred to in the second deed is situated in the mountains east of Vallaki (see chapter 6, &#34;Old Bonegrinder&#34;). The will is signed by Gustav and Elisabeth Durst and bequeathes the house, the windmill, and all other family property to Rosavalda and Thornboldt Durst in the event of their parents' deaths. The books, scrolls, deeds, and will age markedly if taken from the house but remain intact.</p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="treasureparcel" recordname="treasureparcels.id-00079@DD Curse of Strahd">Parcel: Secret Room</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Navigation Shortcuts</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc__curseofstrahd_@DD Curse of Strahd">Root - Curse of Strahd Contents</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_00appendixbintroduction@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Appendix B</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_00areasofthehouse@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Areas of the House</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</enc_18_03_09_secretroom>
			<enc_18_03_10_conservatory>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>10. Conservatory</h>
					<p>Gossamer drapes cover the windows of this elegantly appointed hall, which has a brass-plated chandelier hanging from the ceiling. Upholstered chairs line the walls, and stained-glass wall hangings depict beautiful men, women, and children singing and playing instruments.</p>
					<p>A harpsichord with a bench rests in the northwest corner. Near the fireplace is a large standing harp. Alabaster figurines of well-dressed dancers adorn the mantelpiece. Close inspection of them reveals that several are carvings of well-dressed skeletons.</p>
					<h>Navigation Shortcuts</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc__curseofstrahd_@DD Curse of Strahd">Root - Curse of Strahd Contents</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_00appendixbintroduction@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Appendix B</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_00areasofthehouse@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Areas of the House</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</enc_18_03_10_conservatory>
			<enc_18_03_20_children_sroom>
				<locked type="number">0</locked>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>20. Children's Room</h>
					<p>The door to this room is locked from the outside (see area 16 for details).</p>
					<frame>This room contains a bricked-up window flanked by two dusty, wood-framed beds sized for children. Closer to the door is a toy chest with windmills painted on its sides and a dollhouse that's a perfect replica of the dreary edifice in which you stand. These furnishings are draped in cobwebs. Lying in the middle of the floor are two small skeletons wearing tattered but familiar clothing. The smaller of the two cradles a stuffed doll that you also recognize.</frame>
					<p>The Durst children, Rose and Thorn, were neglected by their parents and locked in this room until they starved to death. Their small skeletons lie in the middle of the floor, plain as day, wearing tattered clothing that the characters recognize as belonging to the children. Thorn's skeleton cradles the boy's stuffed doll.</p>
					<p>The toy chest contains an assortment of stuffed animals and toys. Characters who search the dollhouse and succeed on a DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check find all of the house's secret doors, including one in the attic that leads to a spiral staircase (a miniature replica of area 21).</p>
					<h>Rose and Thorn</h>
					<p>If either the dollhouse or the chest is disturbed, the ghosts of Rose and Thorn appear in the middle of the room. Use the <b>ghost </b>statistics in the <i>Monster Manual, </i>with the following modifications:</p>
					<list>
						<li>The ghosts are Small and lawful good.</li>
						<li>They have 35 (10d6) hit points each.</li>
						<li>They lack the Horrifying Visage action.</li>
						<li>They speak Common and have a challenge rating of 3 (700 XP).</li>
					</list>
					<linklist>
						<link class="imagewindow" recordname="image.id-00126@DD Curse of Strahd">Portrait: Thorn and Rose</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00164@DD Curse of Strahd">NPC: Thorn</link>
						<link class="npc" recordname="npc.id-00163@DD Curse of Strahd">NPC: Rose</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>The children don't like it when the characters disturb their toys, but they fight only in self-defense. Unlike the illusions outside the house, these children know that they're dead. If asked how they died, Rose and Thorn explain that their parents locked them in the attic to protect them from &#34;the monster in the basement,&#34; and that they died from hunger. If asked how one gets to the basement, Rose points to the dollhouse and says, &#34;There's a secret door in the attic.&#34; Characters who then search the dollhouse for secret doors gain advantage on their Wisdom (Perception) checks to find them.</p>
					<p>The children fear abandonment. If one or more characters try to leave, the ghost-children attempt to possess them. If one of the ghosts possesses a character, allow the player to retain control of the character, but assign the character one of the following flaws:</p>
					<list>
						<li>A character possessed by Rose gains the following flaw: &#34;I like being in charge and get angry when other people tell me what to do.&#34;</li>
						<li>A character possessed by Thorn gains the following flaw: &#34;I'm scared of everything, including my own shadow, and weep with despair when things don't go my way.&#34;</li>
					</list>
					<p>A character possessed by the ghost of Rose or Thorn won't willingly leave Death House or the dungeon below it. Both ghosts can be intimidated into leaving their hosts with a successful DC 11 Charisma (Intimidation) check made as an action.</p>
					<p>A ghost reduced to 0 hit points can reform at dawn the next day. The only way to put the children's spirits to rest is to put their skeletal remains in their tombs (areas 23E and 23F). The children don't know this, however.</p>
					<h>Development</h>
					<p>If the party lays the children's spirits to rest, each character gains inspiration (see &#34;Inspiration&#34; in chapter 4, &#34;Personality and Background,&#34; of the <i>Player's Handbook </i>).</p>
					<h>Navigation Shortcuts</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc__curseofstrahd_@DD Curse of Strahd">Root - Curse of Strahd Contents</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_00appendixbintroduction@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Appendix B</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_00areasofthehouse@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Areas of the House</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</enc_18_03_20_children_sroom>
			<enc_18_03_23e_rose_scrypt>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>23E. Rose's Crypt</h>
					<p>The stone slab is etched with the name Rosavalda Durst. The chamber beyond contains an empty coffin on a stone bier.</p>
					<p>If Rose's skeletal remains (see area 20) are placed in the coffin, the child's ghost finds peace and disappears forever. A character possessed by Rose's ghost when this occurs is no longer possessed (see also the &#34;Development&#34; section in area 20).</p>
					<h>Navigation Shortcuts</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc__curseofstrahd_@DD Curse of Strahd">Root - Curse of Strahd Contents</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_00appendixbintroduction@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Appendix B</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_00areasofthehouse@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Areas of the House</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_23_familycrypts@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - 23. Family Crypts</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</enc_18_03_23e_rose_scrypt>
			<enc_18_03_23f_thorn_scrypt>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>23F. Thorn's Crypt</h>
					<p>The stone slab is etched with the name Thornboldt Durst. The chamber beyond contains an empty coffin on a stone bier.</p>
					<p>If Thorn's skeletal remains (see area 20) are placed in the coffin, the child's ghost finds peace and disappears forever. A character possessed by Thorn's ghost when this occurs is no longer possessed (see also the &#34;Development&#34; section in area 20).</p>
					<h>Navigation Shortcuts</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc__curseofstrahd_@DD Curse of Strahd">Root - Curse of Strahd Contents</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_00appendixbintroduction@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Appendix B</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_00areasofthehouse@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Areas of the House</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_23_familycrypts@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - 23. Family Crypts</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</enc_18_03_23f_thorn_scrypt>
			<enc_18_03_26_hiddenspikedpit>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>26. Hidden Spiked Pit</h>
					<p>The ghostly chanting heard throughout the dungeon gets discernibly louder as one heads west along this tunnel. A successful DC 15 Wisdom (Perception) check reveals an absence of footprints. Characters searching the floor for traps find a 5-foot-long, 10-foot-deep pit hidden under several rotted wooden planks, all hidden under a thin layer of dirt. The pit has sharpened wooden spikes at the bottom. The first character to step on the cover falls through, landing prone and taking 3 (1d6) bludgeoning damage from the fall plus 11 (2d10) piercing damage from the spikes.</p>
					<p></p>
					<linklist>
						<link class="battle" recordname="battle.id-00203@DD Curse of Strahd">Encounter: Hidden Spiked Pit Trap</link>
					</linklist>
					<h>Navigation Shortcuts</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc__curseofstrahd_@DD Curse of Strahd">Root - Curse of Strahd Contents</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_00appendixbintroduction@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Appendix B</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_00areasofthehouse@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Areas of the House</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</enc_18_03_26_hiddenspikedpit>
			<enc_18_03_35_reliquary>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<text type="formattedtext">
					<h>35. Reliquary</h>
					<p>The ghostly chant emanating from area 38 fills this room. Characters can discern a dozen or so voices saying, over and over, &#34;He is the Ancient. He is the Land.&#34;</p>
					<p>The cult amassed several &#34;relics&#34; that it used in its rituals. These worthless items are stored in thirteen niches along the walls:</p>
					<list>
						<li>A small, mummified, yellow hand with sharp claws (a goblin's hand) on a loop of rope</li>
						<li>A knife carved from a human bone</li>
						<li>A dagger with a rat's skull set into the pommel</li>
						<li>An 8-inch-diameter varnished orb made from a nothic's eye</li>
						<li>An aspergillum carved from bone</li>
						<li>A folded cloak made from stitched ghoul skin</li>
						<li>A desiccated frog lashed to a stick (could be mistaken for a <i>wand of polymorph </i>)</li>
						<li>A bag full of bat guano</li>
						<li>A hag's severed finger</li>
						<li>A 6-inch-tall wooden figurine of a mummy, its arms crossed over its chest</li>
						<li>An iron pendant adorned with a devil's face</li>
						<li>The shrunken, shriveled head of a halfling</li>
						<li>A small wooden coffer containing a dire wolf's withered tongue</li>
					</list>
					<linklist>
						<link class="treasureparcel" recordname="treasureparcels.id-00087@DD Curse of Strahd">Parcel: Cult &#34;Treasures&#34;</link>
					</linklist>
					<p>The southernmost tunnel slopes down at a 20-degree angle into murky water and ends at a rusty portcullis (area 37).</p>
					<h>Navigation Shortcuts</h>
					<linklist>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc__curseofstrahd_@DD Curse of Strahd">Root - Curse of Strahd Contents</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_00appendixbintroduction@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Appendix B</link>
						<link class="encounter" recordname="encounter.enc_18_03_00areasofthehouse@DD Curse of Strahd">Up - Areas of the House</link>
					</linklist>
				</text>
			</enc_18_03_35_reliquary>
		</category>
		<category name="19. Appendix C: Treasures" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="20. Appendix D: Monsters and NPCs" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="21. Appendix E: The Tarokka Deck" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="22. Appendix F: Handouts" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
	</encounter>
	<image>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - DM Maps" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00068>
				<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
			</id-00068>
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Handouts" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00209>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Strahd's Invitation.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00209>
			<id-00210>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Tome of Strahd 1.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00210>
			<id-00211>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Tome of Strahd 2.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00211>
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Maps" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00004>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
			</id-00004>
			<id-00008>
				<public />
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Map - Church.jpg</bitmap>
					<mask>maskedimages/1512677270.png</mask>
					<gridsize>32</gridsize>
					<gridoffset>27,1</gridoffset>
					<gridsnap>on</gridsnap>
					<shortcuts>
						<shortcut>
							<x>279</x>
							<y>399</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5a_hall@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>219</x>
							<y>454</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5b_doru_sbedroom@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>214</x>
							<y>383</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5c_donavich_sbedroom@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>367</x>
							<y>446</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5d_trapdoor@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>359</x>
							<y>386</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5e_office@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>282</x>
							<y>260</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5f_chapel@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>799</x>
							<y>324</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5g_undercroft@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>797</x>
							<y>103</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5_church@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
					</shortcuts>
					<tokens>
						<idcounter>10</idcounter>
						<tokenlock />
						<scalelock>10</scalelock>
						<token>
							<prototype>tokens/campaign/Donavich.png@DD Curse of Strahd</prototype>
							<id>1</id>
							<x>300</x>
							<y>210</y>
							<unmodifiable />
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>tokens/campaign/Doru.png@DD Curse of Strahd</prototype>
							<id>2</id>
							<x>620</x>
							<y>242</y>
							<unmodifiable />
							<visibilitylocked>off</visibilitylocked>
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>portrait_id-00009_token</prototype>
							<id>6</id>
							<x>300</x>
							<y>242</y>
							<scale>2.56</scale>
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>tokens/campaign/Ismark the Lesser.png@DD Curse of Strahd</prototype>
							<id>10</id>
							<x>268</x>
							<y>242</y>
							<visibilitylocked>on</visibilitylocked>
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>portrait_id-00011_token</prototype>
							<id>3</id>
							<x>300</x>
							<y>290</y>
							<scale>2.56</scale>
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>portrait_id-00007_token</prototype>
							<id>8</id>
							<x>268</x>
							<y>290</y>
							<scale>2.56</scale>
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>portrait_id-00003_token</prototype>
							<id>4</id>
							<x>268</x>
							<y>210</y>
							<scale>2.56</scale>
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>tokens/campaign/Ireena Kolyana.png@DD Curse of Strahd</prototype>
							<id>9</id>
							<x>236</x>
							<y>434</y>
							<visibilitylocked>on</visibilitylocked>
						</token>
						<token>
							<prototype>portrait_id-00006_token</prototype>
							<id>5</id>
							<x>204</x>
							<y>466</y>
							<scale>2.56</scale>
						</token>
					</tokens>
				</image>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
			</id-00008>
			<id-00021>
				<public />
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Map - Village of Barovia.jpg</bitmap>
					<shortcuts>
						<shortcut>
							<x>247</x>
							<y>203</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e6_cemetery@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>246</x>
							<y>369</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e5_church@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>457</x>
							<y>736</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e1_bildrath_smercantile@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>467</x>
							<y>586</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e2_bloodofthevinetavern@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>418</x>
							<y>802</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e3_madmary_stownhouse@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>800</x>
							<y>554</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e7_hauntedhouse@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>386</x>
							<y>1065</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_e4_burgomaster_smansion@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
						<shortcut>
							<x>475</x>
							<y>97</y>
							<class>encounter</class>
							<recordname>encounter.enc_03_02_00areasofthevillage@DD Curse of Strahd</recordname>
						</shortcut>
					</shortcuts>
					<tokens>
						<idcounter>1</idcounter>
						<token>
							<prototype>portrait_id-00011_token</prototype>
							<id>1</id>
							<x>411</x>
							<y>641</y>
							<scale>0.2</scale>
						</token>
					</tokens>
					<pointers>
						<pointer>
							<id>2</id>
							<type>1</type>
							<startx>196</startx>
							<starty>1047</starty>
							<endx>381</endx>
							<endy>1065</endy>
							<owner></owner>
							<color>b95000</color>
						</pointer>
						<pointer>
							<id>4</id>
							<type>4</type>
							<startx>386</startx>
							<starty>1077</starty>
							<endx>425</endx>
							<endy>1033</endy>
							<owner>id-00003</owner>
							<color>ff007d00</color>
						</pointer>
						<pointer>
							<id>3</id>
							<type>1</type>
							<startx>396</startx>
							<starty>669</starty>
							<endx>454</endx>
							<endy>721</endy>
							<owner></owner>
							<color>b95000</color>
						</pointer>
						<pointer>
							<id>4</id>
							<type>1</type>
							<startx>275</startx>
							<starty>786</starty>
							<endx>395</endx>
							<endy>794</endy>
							<owner></owner>
							<color>b95000</color>
						</pointer>
						<pointer>
							<id>5</id>
							<type>1</type>
							<startx>97</startx>
							<starty>494</starty>
							<endx>224</endx>
							<endy>401</endy>
							<owner></owner>
							<color>b95000</color>
						</pointer>
						<pointer>
							<id>1</id>
							<type>1</type>
							<startx>720</startx>
							<starty>530</starty>
							<endx>780</endx>
							<endy>549</endy>
							<owner>id-00006</owner>
							<color>ff6e2dff</color>
						</pointer>
					</pointers>
				</image>
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
			</id-00021>
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Monsters" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00030>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Barovian Witch.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00030>
			<id-00113>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Strahd's Animated Armor.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00113>
			<id-00223>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Black Pudding.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00223>
			<id-00237>
				<public />
			</id-00237>
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - NPCs" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00092>
				<public />
			</id-00092>
			<id-00093>
				<public />
			</id-00093>
			<id-00126>
				<public />
			</id-00126>
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Portraits" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00031>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Barovians.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00031>
			<id-00035>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Count Strahd von Zarovich.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00035>
			<id-00084>
				<public />
			</id-00084>
			<id-00102>
				<public />
			</id-00102>
			<id-00112>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Strahd Epilogue.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00112>
			<id-00114>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Strahd's Crest.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00114>
			<id-00120>
				<public />
				<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
			</id-00120>
			<id-00127>
				<image type="image">
					<bitmap>Tome of Strahd.jpg</bitmap>
				</image>
			</id-00127>
			<id-00132>
				<public />
				<isidentified type="number">1</isidentified>
			</id-00132>
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Tarokka" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00159>
				<public />
			</id-00159>
			<id-00160>
				<public />
			</id-00160>
			<id-00164>
				<public />
			</id-00164>
			<id-00176>
				<public />
			</id-00176>
			<id-00184>
				<public />
			</id-00184>
			<id-00212>
				<public />
			</id-00212>
		</category>
	</image>
	<npc>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - MM" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Monsters" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - NPCs" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00167>
				<locked type="number">1</locked>
				<category name="DD Curse of Strahd" baseicon="0" decalicon="0">
				</category>
			</id-00167>
		</category>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Traps" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
		</category>
	</npc>
	<treasureparcels>
		<category name="Curse of Strahd - Parcels" baseicon="8" decalicon="1">
			<id-00087>
				<category name="DD Curse of Strahd" baseicon="0" decalicon="0">
					<itemlist>
						<category name="DD Curse of Strahd" baseicon="0" decalicon="0">
							<id-00007>
								<isidentified type="number">0</isidentified>
								<locked type="number">1</locked>
								<nonid_name type="string">Wand</nonid_name>
							</id-00007>
						</category>
					</itemlist>
				</category>
			</id-00087>
		</category>
	</treasureparcels>
</root>
